Margaret Bourke-White Papers
Margaret Bourke-White Papers
- Photographs, professional
  - World War II
    - Aerial pictures of America [LIFE Job #15855], 1944 (Box 271, Folder 1-15)
    - Aerial pictures of America [LIFE Job #15855], 1944 (Box 272, Folder 1-15)
    - Aerial pictures of America [LIFE Job #15855], 1944 (Box 273, Folder 1-3)
    - Aerial pictures of America [LIFE Job #15855], 1944 (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
    - Black Society soup kitchen, Rome [LIFE Job #16679] (Box 273, Folder 3-7)
    - Italian politics [LIFE Job #16680], 1944 (Box 206, Folder 12-13)
    - Italian politics [LIFE Job #16680], 1944 (Box 207, Folder 1-6)
    - Black market, Rome [LIFE Job #16685], 1945 (Box 273, Folder 7-11)
    - House Military Affairs Committee visits 5th Army Front [LIFE Job #16689], 1944 (Box 207, Folder 6-9)
    - 5th Army Christmas [LIFE Job #16692], 1944 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - 5th Army Christmas; WACs prepare for Christmas [LIFE Job #16692] (Box 273, Folder 11)
    - Christmas Midnight Mass, St. Peter's [LIFE Job #16731], 1945 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Oratoria San Pietro children's Christmas party [LIFE Job #16732], 1944 (Box 207, Folder 10-11)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and 5th Army [LIFE Job #17036], 1945 (Box 215, Folder 8-9)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and 5th Army [LIFE Job #17036] (Box 274, Folder 1-15)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and 5th Army [LIFE Job #17036] (Box 275, Folder 1-15)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and 5th Army [LIFE Job #17036] (Box 276, Folder 1-15)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and 5th Army [LIFE Job #17036] (Box 277, Folder 1-14)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and 5th Army [LIFE Job #17036] (Box 278, Folder 1-15)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and 5th Army [LIFE Job #17036] (Box 279, Folder 1-15)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and 5th Army [LIFE Job #17036] (Box 280, Folder 1-12)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and 5th Army [LIFE Job #17036] (Oversize 9, Folder 8)
    - Italian royal family; Quirinal; Ambassador Alan Kirk [LIFE Job #17223], 1945; 1948? (Box 280, Folder 12-15)
    - Italian royal family; Quirinal; Ambassador Alan Kirk [LIFE Job #17223], 1945; 1948? (Box 281, Folder 1-15)
    - Italian royal family; Quirinal; Ambassador Alan Kirk [LIFE Job #17223], 1945; 1948? (Box 282, Folder 1-2)
    - Pisa; Royal Palace; San Rosari [LIFE Job #17225], 1945 (Box 283, Folder 1-14)
    - Pisa; Royal Palace; San Rosari [LIFE Job #17225], 1945 (Box 284, Folder 1-7)
    - Vatican [LIFE Job #17226], POW file; restoration of art treasures; general (Box 282, Folder 3-14)
    - Vatican [LIFE Job #17226], POW file; restoration of art treasures; general (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - General George Patton [LIFE Job #17355] (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Train looting, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17357], [1945?] (Box 305, Folder 1-7)
    - Train looting, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17357], [1945?] (Oversize 21, Folder 1)
    - Train looting, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17357], [1945?] (Oversize 21, Folder 5)
    - Cologne essay [LIFE Job #17389], 1945 (Box 284, Folder 7-15)
    - Cologne essay [LIFE Job #17389], 1945 (Box 285, Folder 1-15)
    - Cologne essay [LIFE Job #17389], 1945 (Box 286, Folder 1-12)
    - Cologne essay [LIFE Job #17389], 1945 (Oversize 21, Folder 5)
    - First trial held by military government in Cologne [LIFE Job #17415] (Box 286, Folder 12-15)
    - First trial held by military government in Cologne [LIFE Job #17415] (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Schweinfurt ball bearing factory [LIFE Job #17537] (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Airviews of smoke screens over Rhine [LIFE Job #17538] (Box 287, Folder 1-6)
    - Buchenwald Concentration Camp [LIFE Job #17584] (Box 247, Folder 1-8)
    - Buchenwald Concentration Camp [LIFE Job #17584] (Box 249, Folder 7-8)
    - Buchenwald Concentration Camp [LIFE Job #17584] (Oversize 21, Folder 1-3)
    - Leipzig suicides [LIFE Job #17602], 1945 (Box 287, Folder 6-10)
    - Number Three Erla Work Camp [LIFE Job #17603] (Box 247, Folder 8-16)
    - Number Three Erla Work Camp [LIFE Job #17603] (Box 249, Folder 8)
    - Number Three Erla Work Camp [LIFE Job #17603] (Oversize 21, Folder 1)
    - Number Three Erla Work Camp [LIFE Job #17603] (Oversize 21, Folder 4)
    - Holy Name Society's Christmas party for kids [LIFE Job #17623], Cardinal R. Rossi, E. Galizzi[?], Brigadier General T. K. Brown (Box 273, Folder 12-15)
    - Holy Name Society's Christmas party for kids [LIFE Job #17623], Cardinal R. Rossi, E. Galizzi[?], Brigadier General T. K. Brown (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - "Faceless Fritz"; Allied POWs, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17643], some of this material used in Section V of "Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly" (Box 247, Folder 16)
    - "Faceless Fritz"; Allied POWs, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17643], some of this material used in Section V of "Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly" (Box 248, Folder 1-15)
    - "Faceless Fritz"; Allied POWs, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17643], some of this material used in Section V of "Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly" (Box 249, Folder 1-15)
    - "Faceless Fritz"; Allied POWs, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17643], some of this material used in Section V of "Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly" (Box 250, Folder 1-15)
    - "Faceless Fritz"; Allied POWs, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17643], some of this material used in Section V of "Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly" (Box 251, Folder 1-15)
    - "Faceless Fritz"; Allied POWs, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17643], some of this material used in Section V of "Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly" (Box 252, Folder 1-13)
    - "Faceless Fritz"; Allied POWs, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17643], some of this material used in Section V of "Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly" (Oversize 21, Folder 1)
    - "Faceless Fritz"; Allied POWs, Frankfurt [LIFE Job #17643], some of this material used in Section V of "Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly" (Oversize 21, Folder 4)
    - Bomb damage in Germany [LIFE Job #17698], 1945 (Box 287, Folder 10-15)
    - Bomb damage in Germany [LIFE Job #17698], 1945 (Box 288, Folder 1-15)
    - Bomb damage in Germany [LIFE Job #17698], 1945 (Box 289, Folder 1-15)
    - Bomb damage in Germany [LIFE Job #17698], 1945 (Box 290, Folder 1-15)
    - Bomb damage in Germany [LIFE Job #17698], 1945 (Box 291, Folder 1-15)
    - Bomb damage in Germany [LIFE Job #17698], 1945 (Box 292, Folder 1-15)
    - Bomb damage in Germany [LIFE Job #17698], 1945 (Box 293, Folder 1-15)
    - Bomb damage in Germany [LIFE Job #17698], 1945 (Box 294, Folder 1-11)
    - Goering captured, press conference [LIFE Job #17775], 1945 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - "Face of the Moon" [LIFE Job #17786], 1945; ruined German cities (Box 207, Folder 11-12)
    - Ruhr [LIFE Job #18203], 1945-1946; Krupp family, damage, displaced persons, etc. (Box 294, Folder 12-15)
    - Ruhr [LIFE Job #18203], 1945-1946; Krupp family, damage, displaced persons, etc. (Box 295, Folder 1-15)
    - Ruhr [LIFE Job #18203], 1945-1946; Krupp family, damage, displaced persons, etc. (Box 296, Folder 1-15)
    - Ruhr [LIFE Job #18203], 1945-1946; Krupp family, damage, displaced persons, etc. (Box 297, Folder 1-15)
    - Ruhr [LIFE Job #18203], 1945-1946; Krupp family, damage, displaced persons, etc. (Box 298, Folder 1-15)
    - Ruhr [LIFE Job #18203], 1945-1946; Krupp family, damage, displaced persons, etc. (Box 299, Folder 1-15)
    - Ruhr [LIFE Job #18203], 1945-1946; Krupp family, damage, displaced persons, etc. (Box 300, Folder 1-15)
    - Ruhr [LIFE Job #18203], 1945-1946; Krupp family, damage, displaced persons, etc. (Box 301, Folder 1-14)
    - Dusseldorf track meet [LIFE Job #18259] (Box 301, Folder 14-15)
    - Dusseldorf track meet [LIFE Job #18259] (Box 302, Folder 1-4)
    - Convoy from Archangel (Box 302, Folder 5-15)
    - Convoy from Archangel (Box 303, Folder 1-3)
    - USS Maryland (Box 303, Folder 3-15)
    - Garden party (Box 304, Folder 1-15)
    - Garden party (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Victory parade, Berlin (Box 305, Folder 7-8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 213, Folder 4-10)
    - Miscellaneous, people, bomb damage (Box 305, Folder 8-9)
    - Miscellaneous [includes LIFE Job #14264] (Oversize 11, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, includes "Montgomery" (Oversize 21, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous from "Censor" envelope, trains, factories, damage, people, soldiers, etc.; codes include DEA 2861-2866; DEA 2923-2924; DEA 2928-2930;; DEA 2936-2952; DEA 2985-2986; DEA 2988-2999; note reads "Peggy - The censor left these in my box, said they were stopped. Suggest you take it up with him, if you think they are important" (Box 305, Folder 9-15)
    - Miscellaneous from "Censor" envelope, trains, factories, damage, people, soldiers, etc.; codes include DEA 2861-2866; DEA 2923-2924; DEA 2928-2930;; DEA 2936-2952; DEA 2985-2986; DEA 2988-2999; note reads "Peggy - The censor left these in my box, said they were stopped. Suggest you take it up with him, if you think they are important" (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous contact prints, men, women, children, animals, soldiers, landscapes, buildings, etc. (Box 306, Folder 1-9)
  - Nature series [NAT]
    - Roses, 1940 (Box 306, Folder 9-12)
    - Roses, 1940 (Box 307, Folder 1-10)
    - Ferns, 1940 (Box 307, Folder 10-15)
    - Ferns, 1940 (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - Snakes, 1940 (Box 308, Folder 1-8)
    - Owls and pigeons (Box 308, Folder 8-13)
    - Roses (Box 308, Folder 14-15)
    - Roses (Box 309, Folder 1-2)
    - Falcons and falconry (Box 309, Folder 2-3)
    - Archaeologists, including Mary Whittemore (Box 309, Folder 3-5)
    - Birds (Box 309, Folder 5-8)
    - Butterflies and caterpillars (Box 309, Folder 8-12)
    - Fish (Box 309, Folder 12-14)
    - Butterflies and caterpillars (Box 309, Folder 15)
    - Butterflies and caterpillars (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Buildings (Box 310, Folder 1-2)
    - Birds (Box 310, Folder 2-6)
    - Elephants (Box 310, Folder 6-7)
    - Miscellaneous, mostly birds, probably part of Nature series (Box 310, Folder 7-14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 173, Folder 7-10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1937; moth, probably part of Nature series (Box 173, Folder 10-12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1937; moth, probably part of Nature series (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, praying mantis, probably part of Nature series (Box 174, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 5-6)
    - Interpositives 12014-12180 (Box 372)
    - Interpositives 12181-12480 (Box 373)
    - Interpositives 12481-12720 (Box 374)
    - Interpositives 12721-12955 (Box 375)
  - Miscellaneous / unidentified
    This subseries contains a mix of color transparencies and black-and-white prints and contact prints; subjects include Masons, highways, Carnegie Art Museum, Antigua, Mayan pyramids, and some candid shots of Bourke-White and friends.
    - Miscellaneous contact prints, likely from "You Have Seen Their Faces" [YOU] (Box 310, Folder 14-15)
    - Miscellaneous contact prints, likely from "You Have Seen Their Faces" [YOU] (Box 311, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscelleneous contact prints, folder 4 includes job labeled [SAY] (Box 311, Folder 2-4)
    - Miscellaneous prints from various jobs, includes Nikolai Sokoloff, Johnson estate, St. Louis freight yards, rural scenes, bugle player, industrial subjects, trains (Box 311, Folder 4-8)
    - Miscellaneous prints from various jobs, includes job labeled "13217", woman welder, Turkish general, Russian workers, industrial subjects (Box 311, Folder 9-12)
    - Miscellaneous prints from various jobs, including RUS 315, 317, 318, 319, 324, 329; names include John Harris, Charles Springer, George Dewey, George Gump, W.A. Haven, Alex Graybaugh, Jack Middleton, "Harri[o]", Fred Hayes, B.E. McKechnie (Box 311, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous interpositives [code: UNI], 19778-19834, 19836-19846 (Box 398)
    - [xxx Folders found in OS 121, not in original inventory - are these empty? need to check] (Oversize 21, Folder 5-7)
- Recordings
  - Audiotapes
    - Brief written summary of five of the tapes (Box 107)
      Brief summary of the following give tapes: Norman Ross, "For Women Only" San Joaquin Valley Town Hall, Voice of America. It is unknown who created the summaries; possibly it was prepared by processing staff.
    - For Women Only, Part 1, 5/12/1963; mbw_162; hosted by Lillian Ordman; topics include LIFE cover; awards; how she got started; photographing; Stalin; war experiences; General Doolittle; Gandhi; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 107)
    - For Women Only, Part 2, 5/12/1963; mbw_163; hosted by Lillian Ordman; topics include LIFE cover; awards; how she got started; photographing; Stalin; war experiences; General Doolittle; Gandhi; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 107)
    - Interview from This is NY with Mrs. [illegible], 8/26/1957; mbw_161; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 107)
    - Margaret Bourke-White, mbw_274; contents unknown; Audio cassette (Box 109)
    - Margaret Bourke-White, mbw_275; contents unknown; possibly a reference tape created by SU; Audio cassette (Box 109)
    - Margaret Bourke-White, mbw_279; contents unknown; accompanied by note "MBW deposit 2 cassettes Jonathan Heller c/o Picturescope 12/12/86 may be copied for research purposes JH & CAD"; Audio cassette (Box 109)
    - Margaret Bourke-White Cassette No. 1, 1981; mbw_281; World War II, Russia, Stalin, photography as art form; Audio cassette (Box 109)
      Typed note in case reads as follows: "SIDE 1 - 10-7-38, interview on WOW, Omaha (16" disc). Comments on German invasion of Czechoslovakia, effect of German propaganda, traveling alone in Europe during this time, mechanics of photography, attitudes toward her as a female photographer vs. usual housewife role. 2-22-54 NBC Reference Recording Collector's Item 12" disc 2 sides Photography as an art different from painting, its role in preserving history, the importance of what goes on behind the lens rather than what is in front. SIDE 2 - 16" disc no. 991 Describes visit to USSR to see effect of non-aggression pact just as war broke out; preparations for war; women training for factories, impressions of Moscow air raid, attempts to photograph Stalin. 16" disc, no. 990 Attempt to photograph Stalin cont., impressions of him, discussion of portrait of Stalin's mother, daytime air raid, impressions of the front, banquet before her departure. Re-recorded by William Storm for George Arents Research Library, Feb. 1981 (Dolbyized)
    - Margaret Bourke-White Cassette No. 2, 1981; mbw_282; World War II, bombing missions, women's role in war; Audio cassette (Box 109)
      Typed note in case reads as follows: "SIDE 1 - 5-14-43, LA. Friday Morning (12" discs) Background on her decision to become a war correspondent, aspects of flying on bombing missions - personalities, teamwork, etc., naming and christening the 'Flying Fortress', trip to N. Africa, praise for WACS, WAVES, etc., women's role in the war, account of personal discipling and reaction while aboard a torpedoed ship. SIDE 2 - 5-14-43, L.A. Friday Morning, cont. (12" discs) Comments on Army food, Christmas packages, visits to other airfields, the art of the foxhole, Daniel Boone and the 4 German bombers, her first bombing mission experience. Re-recorded by William Storm for George Arents Research Library, Feb. 1981 (Dolbyized)
    - Margaret Bourke-White cassette #1, mbw_277; contents unknown; possibly a reference tape created by SU; Audio cassette (Box 109)
    - Margaret Bourke-White cassette #2, mbw_278; contents unknown; possibly a reference tape created by SU; Audio cassette (Box 109)
    - Margaret Bourke-White Wilson Hicks Conference, 1958; mbw_280; accompanied by note "MBW deposit 2 cassettes Jonathan Heller c/o Picturescope 12/12/86 may be copied for research purposes JH & CAD"; Audio cassette (Box 109)
    - Margaret Bourke-White Wilson Hicks conference keynote speech from University of Miami Archives, 1958; mbw_276; Audio cassette (Box 109)
    - MBW speaking to children 2 cuts, mbw_164; appears to be preservation copy; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 107)
    - possibly Stanford Blank, possibly practice w/Mrs. E., 1965; mbw_159; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 107)
    - San Joaquin Valley Town Hall series Margaret Bourke-White 7pm, 1/23/1953; mbw_166; primarily Korean War; MBW sings Korean song (”China Night” - about 25 seconds); 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 107)
    - San Joaquin Valley Town Hall, mbw_270; Audio cassette (Box 109)
    - San Joaquin Valley Town Hall, 1953; mbw_272; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 109)
    - Speech therapy tape, mbw_165; Audio cassette (Box 107)
    - VOA with Mr. Alderman, Aug 1963; mbw_002; An Interview with Margaret Bourke-White conducted in August 1963. Topics include beginnings of career at Cornell; beauty of industry/machines; on being a woman; inspirations; difficulties in various shoots; emotion in her photos; advice to young people; trends in modern photographic equipment; description of her study; book.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 107)
    - WBKB-TC (Chicago) Norman Ross Show, 9/16/1963; mbw_160; topics include MBW childhood and early life; LIFE, Fortune and TIME covers; Parkinson's Disease and therapy; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 107)
    - Your Women's Page of the Air, May 1963; mbw_273; Audio cassette (Box 109)
    - Your Women's Page of the Air parts 1 & 2 5/63 Tape 1 / Norman Ross (TV); NYS Dept of Commerce spot; Voice of America; This is New York, 1963; mbw_271; Audio cassette (Box 109)
  - Dictation discs
    These are small green plastic discs, varying in size, created on a dictation machine of unknown make and model. Many are clipped to an envelope, perhaps that in which they were originally sent. There are annotations, done by an unknown person, on many of the new archival sleeves; these notes may or may not accurately reflect the actual content. ID numbers for the discs are given in parentheses. For an itemized listing, contact the repository listed above.
    - Miscellaneous, notes on sleeves include the following words and phrases: early dictating on bk and Italy government, singing disks, Gilbert and Sullivan; mbw_003 through mbw_018; 16 items (Box 106)
    - "Voice and Hand", notes on sleeves include the following words and phrases: Sacramento, Jap. Luncheon, May Day riot, Col. Henderson, Prof. [illegible] LA Times, machine gun, one BB, lib paper, Beklerim, grand opening, SAC, children grow up trained [illegible]; mbw_019 through mbw_026; 8 items (Box 106)
    - "Recording flying flitgun[?] & Mission", notes on sleeves include the following words and phrases: lecture, SF town hall; mbw_027 through mbw_032; 6 items (Box 106)
    - "Disks for speech practice only and Mr. Kline", notes on sleeves include the following words and phrases: notes, speeches, Korea song, to Mrs Barbara Warner, not needed; mbw_033 through mbw_060; 28 items (Box 106)
    - "Korean discs - Book", 1960-1963; notes on sleeves include the following words and phrases: notebook sides A-D, speech, trial, Henry Simon, speech practice before Wisc speech, Life with Father.; mbw_001; mbw_061 through mbw_093; 34 items (Box 106)
    - "Personal letters - ans.", 1962-1963; 1968,; undated; notes on sleeves include the following words and phrases: Sacramento disk, Japanese song, happy Easter from MBW, for Harriet's nieces, practice read aloud, notebook 8, D.R. Solomon; mbw_094 through mbw_108; 15 items (Box 106)
    - "Daily work on speech", notes on sleeves include the following words and phrases: Wisc speech, speech practice, war between children, speech Mr Carini, speech Mrs Lord and BW together, women guerrillas, Berkeley Women's City Club, BW song to Miki, Fountain A, funny disk with Andres, Los Angeles; mbw_109 through mbw_147; 39 items (Box 106)
    - "Wm. Thomas Cleveland ", 3/8/53; mbw_148 (Box 106)
    - Miscellaneous, mbw_151 through mbw_158; includes typed transcripts of some discs; topics include Bourke-White's involvement with the early days of LIFE magazine, Peggy Smith Sargent, Bourke-White's studio. Some discs appear to be chapters from her book; 8 items (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - [untitled, contents unknown], mbw_149 (Box 106)
    - [untitled, contents unknown], mbw_150 (Box 106)
  - Moving image recordings
    - Eyes on Russia (From the Caucasus to Moscow), mbw_267; "Photographed and produced under the personal direction of Miss Margaret Bourke White."; video transfer from original film; VHS; black and white; sound; 00:12:00. (Box 108)
      Digital version available.
    - Galen Drake Show, mbw_268; Film: 16mm; black and white; sound; 1100 feet.
    - Margaret Bourke-White One Hour Special, WVIZ-TV, Cleveland, mbw_265; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; color; sound; 00:60:00. (Box 108)
    - Margaret Bourke-White: The Humanitarian Vision, mbw_266; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; color; sound; 00:06:00. (Box 108)
    - Margaret Bourke-White: The Humanitarian Vision, 1984; mbw_269; VHS; color; sound; 00:05:50 (Box 108)
    - Person to Person (CBS News), 09/02/1955; mbw_264; June Allyson and Dick Powell; Margaret Bourke-White; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; black and white; sound; 00:30:00. (Box 108)
    - Wendy Waldroup "god child extraordinaire" de Peggy Bourke-White (for Margaret Bourke-White), mbw_263; Film: 16mm film; color; silent; 50 feet.
      Duplicate film. Home movie of woman and child. Return address indicates it was sent from Major and Mrs. M.M. Waldroup, HQ 24th Composite Wing, Borinquen Field, PR (an army base in Puerto Rico). Based on the return address information on the film box and a search in Ancestry.com, the individuals in the movie are probably Cricket Canon (the mother, married to Marvin Martin Waldroup, i.e. "M M Waldroup") and Wendy Waldroup (the child), whose name is listed explicitly on the box. MBW was Wendy's godmother.
  - Phonodiscs
    Titles are taken directly from the items. For an itemized listing, contact the repository listed above.
    - Damaged discs, miscellaneous (Oversize 68)
    - Damaged discs, miscellaneous (Oversize 69)
    - Air Force, parts 1 through 13, 5-14-43; mbw_170 through mbw_176; 7 discs
    - Bill Leonard Interview of Margaret Bourke-White; CBS, mbw_252; 1 side; 1 disc
    - Churchill Speech, mbw_240, mbw_241; 2 discs
      One disc is restricted due to condition.
    - Collector's Item, 2-22-54; mbw_169; 1 disc
    - Despatch [sic] for C.B.S. Margaret Bourke White Parts 1-4, R.T. India, 9/12/47; mbw_189, mbw_190; 2 discs
    - The End of The Act with Erskine Caldwell, Parts 3 and 5; WJZ, 5/21/42; mbw_203; 1 disc
    - Hi Jinx Show; Margaret Bourke White and Lord John Hope; Sides 1-6, 6/15/49; mbw_207, mbw_208, mbw_209; 3 discs
    - Hi Jinx; Guest: Margaret Bourke White. Parts 1-4, June 14, 1949; mbw_210, mbw_211; 2 discs
    - India, parts 1 through 13, mbw_177 through mbw_183; 7 discs
    - India, part 14 and 15, mbw_184, mb_185; 1 disc
      Discs are unlabeled, but presumed to be part of the India set due to location and number of sides reported in inventory. Single sided discs.
    - Interview with Margaret Bourke-White and Erskine Caldwell by Andre Baruch, CBS, parts 1 and 2, 21 January 1942; mbw_167, mbw_168; 2 discs
    - Interview Radio Bazaar Program Jean Colbert and Margaret Bourke-White Parts 1 and 2, undated; mbw_206; 1 disc
    - Kate Smith Hour; M.B.W. Parts 1 and 2, mbw_196; 1 disc
    - Margaret Arlen Show; CBS; 8:30-9:00AM; Parts 2 and 4, 6-1-49; mbw_245; 1 disc
    - Margaret Bourke-White; Wow, Omaha, 10-7-38; mbw_251; 1 side; 1 disc
    - Margaret Bourke-White, 3/29/44; mbw_230 through mbw_237; Single-sided disc.; 8 discs
    - Margaret Bourke-White parts 1-4, 2/11/48; mbw_186, mbw_187; 2 discs
    - Margaret Bourke White; George V. Denny, Jr.; W.Q.X.R., Parts 1-4, 11/21/41; mbw_192, mbw_193; 2 discs
    - Margaret Bourke White; If I Had The Chance; W.J.Z., Parts 1 and 2, 9/2/38; mbw_194; 1 disc
    - Margaret Bourke-White Interviewed by Vesta Eales; W.A.B.C. Parts 1-3, 7/2/42; mbw_202, mbw_262; 2 discs
    - Margaret Bourke White on NBC Blue network - Let Yourself Go with Milton Berle; Bourke-White 13-1, mbw_242, mbw_243; 2 discs
    - Margaret Bourke White; Show of Yesterday And Today, W.J.Z., mbw_191; 1 disc